<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to My Site on Stephen Redding</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome to My Site on Stephen Redding</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Red Team Operator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/crto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/crto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holders of the Red Team Operator badge have demonstrated their knowledge of adversary simulation, command &amp;amp; control, engagement planning and time management. They can perform each stage of an attack lifecycle from initial compromise, to full domain takeover, data hunting, and exfiltration; whilst being aware of OPSEC concerns and bypassing defences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/oscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/oscp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An OSCP has demonstrated the ability to use persistence, creativity, and perceptiveness to identify vulnerabilities and execute organized attacks under tight time constraints. They can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use information gathering techniques to identify and enumerate targets running various operating systems and services&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write scripts and tools to aid in the penetration testing process&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analyze, correct, modify, cross-compile, and port public exploit code&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conduct remote, local privilege escalation, and client-side attacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify and exploit XSS, SQL injection, and file inclusion vulnerabilities in web applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leverage tunneling techniques to pivot between networks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OSCP holders have also shown they can think outside the box while managing both time and resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/cios/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/cios/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earners of the CompTIA IT Operations Specialist (CIOS) certification have the ability to manage&#xA;the flow of a workplace and optimize day-to-day activities. These IT operations specialists have demonstrated the ability to analyze business operations and identify customer needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/network&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/network&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA Network+ earners who certified prior to January 1, 2011 have a Network+ considered&#xA;good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners of the&#xA;CompTIA Network+ certification have the skills needed to troubleshoot, configure, and manage&#xA;enterprise networks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/a&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/a&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA A+ earners who certified between January 1993 and December 31, 2010, have an A+&#xA;considered good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners&#xA;of the CompTIA A+ certification have validated skills in hardware repair and configuration, PC&#xA;and peripheral troubleshooting, Windows operating system administration, and user support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A timeless call to help others led me to a lifelong fascination with beliefs and their profound impact on our lives. At the core of everything I do is the belief that the mind shapes our outcomes. My journey has been one of deep exploration, where I’ve come to understand how both the technical and the personal are reflections of the same underlying principles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From an early age, I was told to never ask questions about belief systems. That advice only fueled my curiosity. After years of exploring various ideologies, I came to a powerful realization: it wasn’t the specific diets, chemicals, or spiritual frameworks that held the key. The true power lay in understanding the underlying mechanics of the mind.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/interests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/interests/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My interests revolve around exploring the deep intersections of thought, belief, and personal transformation. I’m drawn to subjects that challenge conventional thinking and offer a new lens through which to view reality. Whether it’s examining how subconscious patterns influence behavior or studying the subtle energetics of the mind, I’m continually seeking knowledge that sharpens both practical insight and spiritual wisdom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the core of my work is a fascination with how internal states—thoughts, beliefs, and perceptions—shape external realities. I’m always looking for ways to help others unlock this understanding, empowering them to move beyond limitations they may not even realize exist. The underlying principles of self-awareness, personal agency, and conscious creation are what drive my curiosity and passion, whether I’m solving technical problems or guiding others through inner breakthroughs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get In Touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or would like to learn more about my services, feel free to reach out via email. Whether it’s for IT consultation, personal coaching, or exploring the power of beliefs and transformation, I’m happy to connect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can contact me at:&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:stephen.redding31@gmail.com&#34;&gt;stephen.redding31@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I look forward to hearing from you!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
