<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Certifications on Stephen Redding</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Certifications on Stephen Redding</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/certifications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Red Team Operator</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/crto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/crto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holders of the Red Team Operator badge have demonstrated their knowledge of adversary simulation, command &amp;amp; control, engagement planning and time management. They can perform each stage of an attack lifecycle from initial compromise, to full domain takeover, data hunting, and exfiltration; whilst being aware of OPSEC concerns and bypassing defences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSCP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/oscp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/oscp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An OSCP has demonstrated the ability to use persistence, creativity, and perceptiveness to identify vulnerabilities and execute organized attacks under tight time constraints. They can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use information gathering techniques to identify and enumerate targets running various operating systems and services&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write scripts and tools to aid in the penetration testing process&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analyze, correct, modify, cross-compile, and port public exploit code&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conduct remote, local privilege escalation, and client-side attacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify and exploit XSS, SQL injection, and file inclusion vulnerabilities in web applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leverage tunneling techniques to pivot between networks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OSCP holders have also shown they can think outside the box while managing both time and resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIOS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/cios/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/cios/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Earners of the CompTIA IT Operations Specialist (CIOS) certification have the ability to manage&#xA;the flow of a workplace and optimize day-to-day activities. These IT operations specialists have demonstrated the ability to analyze business operations and identify customer needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/network&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/network&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA Network+ earners who certified prior to January 1, 2011 have a Network+ considered&#xA;good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners of the&#xA;CompTIA Network+ certification have the skills needed to troubleshoot, configure, and manage&#xA;enterprise networks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/certifications/a&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/certifications/a&#43;/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CompTIA A+ earners who certified between January 1993 and December 31, 2010, have an A+&#xA;considered good-for-life (GFL). It does not expire and does not have CE requirements. Earners&#xA;of the CompTIA A+ certification have validated skills in hardware repair and configuration, PC&#xA;and peripheral troubleshooting, Windows operating system administration, and user support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
